Guide to the News Service Biographical Files, circa 1930s - 2004 UA.27.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Pieper, Carl F., 1998 (Box 92)
- Pieper, Carl F., 2002 (Box 92)
- Pierce, Catherine (Box 154)
- Pierce, F. Grainger (Box 138)
- Pierce, F. Grainger, d. 10/30/1958, Trustee (Box 117)
- Pierce, J. Jeffrey (Box 92)
- Pierce-Baker, Charlotte (Box 92)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 1999
- Pietrantoni, J.G. (Box 92)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Auxillaries
- Pietrantoni, J.G. (Box 138)
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1965-1969
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1970
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1973
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1974-1977
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1979
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1980
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1981
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1982
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1983-84
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1984
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1985
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1986
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 93)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1987
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1988
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1989
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1991
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1992
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1993
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1994-
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist, 1999
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Geologist
- Pilkey, Orrin H. (Box 138)
- Pilkington, Theo C. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineering, died 1/6/1993
- Pilkington, Theo C. (Box 138)
- Pincher, Felix J. (Box 138)
- Pine, Leo (Box 43)
- Pine, Leo (Box 138)
- Pine, Leo (Box 154)
- Pinkerton, Margaret Isabel (Box 43)
- Pinkerton, Margaret Isabel (Box 138)
- Pinnell, Sheldon R. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatologist
- Pinnell, Sheldon R. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Dermatologist, 2001
- Pinnix, Robert H. (Box 154)
- Pinnix, Robert H., Trustee (Box 117)
- Piot, Charles D. (Box 94)
- Piper, Don C. (Box 43)
- Piper, Otto A. (Box 43)
- Pincher, Felix J. (Box 154)
- Pincher, Felix J. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist
- Pirrung, Michael C. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemist, 1990-2001
- Piscitelli, Joanne (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Gynecologist, 1985
- Pisetsky, David Stephen (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Rheumatology and Immunology, 1985-2000
- Pitman, Kathy C. (Box 94)
- Pittillo, Robert A. (Box 43)
- Pitts, Elizabeth LaRocca (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, 2001
- Pitts, William R. (Box 43)
- Pitts, William R. (Box 138)
- Pitts, William R., d. 4/1960, Trustee (Box 117)
- Piva, John J. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of the for Alumni Affairs and Development, 1987-1991
- Pizzo, Salvatore (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology and Biochemistry, -2001
- Platt, Jeffrey L. (Box 94)
- Pledger, (Detective) M.A. (Box 43)
- Pless, John G. (Box 43)
- Pless, John G. (Box 138)
- Pless, John G. (Box 154)
- Plonsey, Robert (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineering; Physiology
- Plumb, Bruce (Box 43)
- Plummer, Ellen (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Women's Center
- Poirier, Jacques Charles (Box 138)
- Poirier, Jacques Charles (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemist, 1956-76
- Polanyi, Michael (Box 43)
- Polanyi, Michael (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion, 1963
- Polascik, Thomas (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Urology, 2002
- Politano, Victor A. (Box 43)
- Politano, Victor A. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Urology, 1962
- Politano, Victor A. (Box 138)
- Politi, Elisabetta, 2001 (Box 94)
- Pollack, Sheldon V. (Box 94)
- Polniaszck, Richard Paul (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemist
- Polt, Sarah S. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathology, 1960s
- Polyanyi, Michael (Box 138)
- Pondy, Louis R. (Box 43)
- Pope, Deborah (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 1985-97
- Pope, Deborah (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 2001
- Pope, Hilda (Box 43)
- Pope, Liston (Box 43)
- Popkin, Richard H. (Box 43)
- Porter, Calvin Lewis (Box 138)
- Porter, Calvin Lewis (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, 1961-62
- Porter, Earl W. (Box 43)
- Porter, Earl W. (Box 154)
- Porter, F. Ross (Box 43)
- Porter, F. Ross (Box 138)
- Porter, F. Stanley (Box 43)
- Porter, F. Stanley (Box 154)
- Porter, Hubbard Braxton, Trustee (Box 117)
- Porter, Joseph (Box 138)
- Porter, Joseph (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 1985-2001
- Porter, Ned Allen (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemist, 1980s
- Porter, Ross (Box 154)
- Portes, Alejandro (Box 43)
- Portwood, Richard M. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine, 1958-71
- Portwood, Richard M. (Box 138)
- Postlethwait, Raymond W. (Box 43)
- Postlethwait, Raymond W. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgeon, 1989
- Postlethwait, Raymond W. (Box 138)
- Postma, Herman, Trustee 1987-1993, Trustee (Box 117)
- Postman, Herman (Box 138)
- Poston, Mary (Box 43)
- Poston, Mary (Box 154)
- Posy, Carl J. (Box 94)
- Poteat, James D. (Box 43)
- Poteat, James Douglas (Box 154)
- Poteat, Mary (Box 43)
- Poteat, Mary (Box 138)
- Poteat, Mary (Box 154)
- Poteat, William (Box 138)
- Poteat, William (Box 154)
- Poteat, William (Box 94)
- Potter, Michael R. (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1986
- Potter, Michael R. (Box 138)
- Pouagare, Marios C. (Box 43)
- Pounds, Lois (Box 94)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pediatrics; Medical Education, 1996
- Powell, Benjamin Edward, 2 folders (Box 43)
- Powell, Benjamin Edward (Box 138)
- Powell, Benjamin Edward (Box 154)
- Powell, H. Jefferson (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law and Divinity, 1991-2000
- Powell, Richard J. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Art History, of art history dept. through June 30 1999
- Powell, Rufus H., III (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Secretary, 1994
- Powell, Rufus H., III (Box 43)
- Powell, Rufus H., III (Box 138)
- Powell, Rufus H., III (Box 154)
- Powell, Thomas (Box 43)
- Prangue, Harry D. (Box 43)
- Prangue, Harry D. (Box 138)
- Pratt, Edmund T., Jr. (Box 138)
- Pratt, Edmund T., Jr., Trustee (Box 117)
- Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 43)
- Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Office of Cultural Affairs, 1990
- Pratt, Ella Fountain (Box 138)
- Pratt, J. Gaither (Box 43)
- Pratt, J. Gaither (Box 138)
- Pratt, Lanier (Box 43)
- Pratt, Lanier (Box 138)
- Pratt, Lanier (Box 154)
- Pratt, Philip C. (Box 154)
- Pratt, Philip C. (Box 95)
- Pratt, Philip C. (Box 138)
- Pratt, Vernon Gaither (Box 138)
- Pratt, Vernon Gaither (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Art, died 2/27/2000
- Pratt, Walter F. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law, 1984
- Predmore, Richard L. (Box 154)
- Predmore, Richard L. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Grad Arts and Sciences
- Predmore, Richard L. (Box 138)
- Predmore, Richard Lionel (Box 44)
- Preiss, Jack J. (Box 44)
- Preiss, Jack J. (Box 138)
- Preiss, Jack J. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology, 1987
- Preston, Richard A. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Canadian Studies
- Preston, Richard Arthur (Box 44)
- Preston, Richard Arthur (Box 138)
- Preston, Richard Arthur (Box 154)
- Preston, William (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatry, 1979
- Price, David Eugene (Box 138)
- Price, David Eugene (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1974-84
- Price, David Eugene (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1985
- Price, David Eugene (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1986
- Price, David Eugene (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1987-92
- Price, David Eugene (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1993-
- Price, James L., Jr. (Box 138)
- Price, James L., Jr. (Box 44)
- Price, James L., Jr. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Religion, 1974-96
- Price, Mary Kathleen (Kathie) (Box 138)
- Price, Mary Kathleen (Kathie) (Box 44)
- Price, Matthew (Box 95)
- Price, Reynolds (Box 138)
- Price, Reynolds (Box 95)
- Pride, Cletis (Box 44)
- Pride, Cletis (Box 138)
- Pride, Cletis (Box 154)
- Pride, Cletis (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke University News Service, 1969-84
- Prioletti, Vienna (Box 44)
- Prioletti, Vienna (Box 138)
- Prisant, Michael (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Chemistry, 1990-97
- Pritchard, Eric (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music, 1995-96
- Pritchett, Edward (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiologist, 1984-98
- Proctor, Arthur Marcus (Box 44)
- Proctor, C. K. (Box 138)
- Proctor, C. K., Trustee July 1977, Trustee (Box 117)
- Proctor, Jesse H., Jr. (Box 154)
- Proctor, Jesse H., Jr. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Political Science, 1958
- Proctor, Jesse H., Jr. (Box 138)
- Proctor, Jesse Harris, Jr. (Box 44)
- Proctor, Samuel DeWitt (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity, died 5/22/1997
- Proia, Alan (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Opthamologist; Pathologist, 1984
- Prosnitz, Leonard R. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist, 1984-1996
- Protter, Phillip E. (Box 44)
- Proud, Paul P. (Box 44)
- Pryor, David M. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiologist, 1991-94
- Pugh, Stefan M. (Box 95)
- Pullias, Earl Vivon (Box 44)
- Puma, Joseph A. (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cardiologist, 1995
- Pupkin, Marcos J. (Box 44)
- Purohit, Debu (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Fuqua Business, Marketing, 1991-2002
- Purves, Dale (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurobiologist, 1990-2000
- Putallaz, Martha (Box 95)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychologist, 1986-1993
- Putman, Charles E. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist; Vice Provost, 1985-92
- Putman, Charles E. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist; Vice Provost, 1993-99
- Pyatt, Tim (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: University Archivist, 2002
- Pye, Kenneth, 3 folders (Box 44)
- Pye, Kenneth (Box 138)
- Pye, Kenneth A. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: President Duke and SMU, 1987-94
- Pyne, James Minitree (Box 138)
- Pyne, James Minitree (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Duke Hospital, 1949-56
- Quaintance, Richard E., Jr. (Box 44)
- Qualls, Robert G. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: the Environment, 1994
- Queen, Vergil (Box 44)
- Quill, Timothy J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anesthesiology, 1985-89
- Quilligan, Maureen (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English Dept., 1999-2000
- Quin, Louis D. (Box 44)
- Quin, Louis D. (Box 138)
- Quin, Louis D. (Box 96)
- Quinlan, Alician Veronica (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Engineering (biochemical and mechanical)
- Quinn, Galen W. (Box 44)
- Quinn, Galen W. (Box 138)
- Quinn, Galen W. (Box 154)
- Quinn, Naomi (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anthropologist
- Quynn, Dorothy Mackay (Box 44)
- Quynn, Dorothy Mackay (Box 138)
- Quynn, Dorothy Mackay (Box 154)
- Quynn, William Rogers (Box 44)
- Quynn, William Rogers (Box 138)
- Raben, Milton (Box 44)
- Rabin, David (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Engineer, 1957
- Radin, Max (Box 44)
- Radin, Max (Box 138)
- Radtke, Rodney A. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Neurologist, 1995
- Radway, Janice A. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Literature and English, 1994-99
- Raetz, Christian R. H. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemist, 1993-2001
- Raimi, Frederic B. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Cellist, 1974-98
- Raimi, Frederic B. (Box 138)
- Raimi, Mary Eliza Jane (professional name: Jane Hawkins) (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music Dept.
- Rainey, Harry "Uncle Harry" (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, died 3/17/1993
- Rainey, Harry "Uncle Harry" (Box 138)
- Rainey, Thomas B., Jr. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Historian, 1966-67
- Rainwater, Roland W. (Box 96)
- Rainwater, Roland William (Box 45)
- Rainwater, Roland William (Box 138)
- Raitt, Jill (Box 45)
- Raitt, Jill (Box 138)
- Raitt, Jill (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Theology, 1975-80
- Raj, Ganesh (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Urologist, 2002
- Rajagopal, R. (Box 45)
- Rajagopalan, K. V. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemist, 1977-85
- Ralston, Charles W. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry School, 1983
- Ralston, Charles William (Box 45)
- Ralston, Charles William (Box 138)
- Ralston, Charles William (Box 154)
- Ram, (Major) C.H. (Box 45)
- Ram, Panol Chir (Box 45)
- Ramirez-Rivera, Jose (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Medicine, 1969
- Ramsey, Sarah H. (Box 45)
- Ramus, Joseph S. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Botanist, 1985-2000
- Randall, Dale B. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: English, 1960-99
- Randall, Dale B. (Box 138)
- Raney, Richard B. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Othopaedics, 1941
- Raney, Richard B. (Box 138)
- Raney, Richard Beverly (Box 45)
- Rankin, Robert S., 3 folders (Box 45)
- Rankin, Thomas S. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Doc. Studies, 1998-99
- Rankin, Watson Smith (Box 139)
- Rankin, Watson Smith (Box 154)
- Rankin, Watson Smith [Duke Endowment Trustee], d. 9/8/1970, Trustee (Box 117)
- Rankin, William W., Jr. (Box 45)
- Ranson, Guy Harvey (Box 45)
- Ranson, Guy Harvey (Box 139)
- Ranson, Guy Harvey (Box 154)
- Ranson, Russell (Box 45)
- Ranson, Russell (Box 139)
- Ranson, Russell (Box 154)
- Rao, K.R. (Box 45)
- Rao, Sunil (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Doctor, 2002
- Rapaport, Elizabeth (Box 96)
- Raper, Edward S. (Box 45)
- Rappaport, Josephine (Box 45)
- Rasmussen, Ann Marie (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Germanic Language
- Raspberry, William (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Journalism, 1995-2001
- Raspberry, William (Box 96)
- Ratchford, Benjamin Ulysses, 2 folders (Box 45)
- Ratchford, Benjamin Ulysses (Box 139)
- Ratchford, Benjamin Ulysses (Box 154)
- Rath, John (Box 45)
- Rath, John (Box 139)
- Rath, John (Box 154)
- Rauch, Henry E. (Box 139)
- Rauch, Henry E., Trustee (Box 117)
- Rauckman, Elmer J. (Box 45)
- Rausher, Mark D. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoologist, 1989
- Ravin, Carl E. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist, 1978-85
- Ravin, Carl E. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist, 1991
- Ravitz, L.J. (Box 139)
- Ravitz, L.J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatrist, 1951
- Ravitz, L.J. (Box 45)
- Rawlings, Jame, 1998 (Box 96)
- Ray, Mel (Box 45)
- Raymond, Mary Louis (Box 45)
- Raymond, Mary Louis (Box 139)
- Raymond, Mary Louis (Box 154)
- Raynor, Calla Ann (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Health, P.E. and Recreation, 1968
- Read, Andrew (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biologist
- Read, Frank Thompson (Box 45)
- Read, Frank Thompson (Box 139)
- Read, Frank Thompson (Box 154)
- Reagan, Janet M. (Box 45)
- Reamer, I. Thomas (Box 45)
- Reamer, I. Thomas (Box 139)
- Reamer, I. Thomas (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pharmacist, 1968
- Reardon, Kenneth James (Box 45)
- Reardon, Kenneth James (Box 139)
- Reckhow, Kenneth H. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Civil Engineer, 1996-2000
- Reckless, John (Box 46)
- Reckless, John (Box 139)
- Reckless, John (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatrist, 1974
- Redding, Francis (Box 46)
- Redding, Francis (Box 154)
- Redding, Francis (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Music Dept., 1969
- Redding, Francis (Box 139)
- Reddy, William M. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Historian, 1980-96
- Redick, Lloyd F. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anesthesiology and Obstetrics and Gynecology Depts.
- Reed, Frederick J. (Box 154)
- Reed, Frederick J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Engineer
- Reed, Frederick Jerome (Box 46)
- Reed, Mark D. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Sociology, 1991-92
- Reed, Michael Charles (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, 1974-
- Reed, Wallace Elzie (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Economist, 1996
- Reedy, Michael K. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anatomy; Physiology, 2001
- Reents-Budet, Dorie (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Art Museum
- Rees, Joe Curtis (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Librarian, 1971
- Reeves, Robert J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Radiologist, 1962
- Reeves, Robert J. (Box 139)
- Reeves, Robert James (Box 46)
- Reichenberg-Hackett, Wally (Box 46)
- Reichenberg-Hackett, Wally (Box 154)
- Reichert, William M. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biomedical Engineer, 1988
- Reid, Elizabeth Brooks (Box 139)
- Reid, Elizabeth Brooks [Chairman, Institutional Advancement Committee], Trustee 1981-1993, Trustee (Box 117)
- Reid, J.H. Stewart (Box 46)
- Reid, John T. (Box 46)
- Reid, John T. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Spanish, 1940
- Reif, John H. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Computer Science, 1987-2000
- Reilly, Edward (Box 139)
- Reilly, Edward (Box 154)
- Reilly, Edward (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law, 1972
- Reimann, Donald H. (Box 46)
- Reimann, Donald H. (Box 96)
- Reimann, Donald H. (Box 139)
- Reimer, Keith (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathologist, 1983
- Reinhardt, Uwe E., Trustee (Box 117)
- Reintgen, Douglas (Box 46)
- Reinthal, Peter (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Zoologist, 1986
- Reisner, Emily (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathologist, 1982-85
- Reiss, Edmund A. (Box 46)
- Reiter, Mary (Box 46)
- Reller, L. Barth (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Pathologist, 1997-98
- Renager, Burt W., Jr. (Box 46)
- Reppy, William Amell, Jr. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Law, 1980-97
- Reppy, William Amell, Jr. (Box 139)
- Rerych, Stephen K. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgeon
- Reuben, Lucy (Box 46)
- Reuben-Cooke, Wilhelmina M., Trustee 1989, Trustee (Box 117)
- Reveley, W. Taylor, Jr. (Box 113)
  Biographical information. Alumnus; President, Hampden Sydney College
- Reves, Joseph Gerald (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Anesthesiology, 1984-90
- Reynolds, Jacqueline (Box 96)
- Reynolds, Jacqueline (Box 139)
- Reynolds, James (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Botanist, 1996-99
- Reynolds, Thomas D. (Box 46)
- Reynolds, William Neal (Box 139)
- Reynolds, William Neal, d. 9/1951, Trustee (Box 117)
- Reznick, Bruce A. (Box 46)
- Rezvani, Amir (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: UNC, 1999
- Rhine, Joseph Banks, 5 folders (Box 46)
- Rhine, Joseph Banks, 9 folders (Box 47)
- Rhine, Joseph Banks, 3 folders (Box 48)
- Rhine, Joseph Banks (Box 139)
- Rhine, Joseph Banks (Box 154)
- Rhine, Louise (Box 48)
- Rhoades, John MacFarlane (Box 139)
- Rhoads, John MacFarlane (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Psychiatrist, 1962-80
- Rhoads, John MacFarlane (Box 48)
- Rhyne, Charles S. (Box 139)
- Rhyne, Charles S. (Box 154)
- Rhyne, Charles S., Trustee (Box 117)
- Rice, Charles Lynvel (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, 1968
- Rice, Douglas (Box 48)
- Rice, Henry (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Surgeon, 2002
- Rice, John Russell (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Rheumatology; Immunology, 1978
- Rice, Louise (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Art History, 1994-95
- Richard, Carole (Box 48)
- Richard, Jean Francois (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Statistics and Decision Science, 1989
- Richards, George J. (Box 48)
- Richards, John F. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Historian
- Richards, John F. (Box 139)
- Richardson, Curtis J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1975-99
- Richardson, Curtis J. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2001
- Richardson, Curtis J. (Box 139)
- Richardson, David C. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry, 1991-
- Richardson, Jane S. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry, Before 1993
- Richardson, Jane S. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Biochemistry, 1993-
- Richardson, Lawrence, Jr. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Classical Studies, 1966-86
- Richardson, Lawrence, Jr. (Box 139)
- Richardson, Robert, Trustee (Box 117)
- Richey, McMurry Smith (Box 139)
- Richey, McMurry Smith (Box 154)
- Richey, McMurry Smith (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, 1956-1982
- Richey, Russell Earle (Box 96)
- Richey, Russell Earle (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Divinity School, 1994
- Richter, Daniel (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Forestry and Environmental Science, 1988-2001
- Richtsmeier, William (Box 96)
- Ricketts, Mac L. (Box 48)
- Ricketts, Mac L. (Box 139)
- Ricks, William E. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Business, 1985
- Ricks, William E. (Box 139)
- Riddel, Joseph (Box 48)
- Riddel, Joseph (Box 139)
- Riddel, Joseph (Box 155)
- Riddell, Richard V. (Box 155)
- Riddell, Richard V. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama, Before 1993
- Riddell, Richard V. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama, 1993
- Riddell, Richard V. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff: Drama, 1994
- Riedel, John D. (Box 96)
  Biographical information. Faculty/Staff, retired 12/31/87
- Riedel, Eberhard Karl (Box 48)